Hey Ryan,
Ian had a chuckle about your tann
a nudge about it. So here's your nudge.
>> Appreciate it. Yeah, he's always got
jokes. No, it's it's actually
interesting. We moved our college
meetings um a week ahead of the Super
Bowl
to really create a little bit of space
for my entire staff to get away, get
some clarity so that when we get back
from here, we're ready to roll um and
have a clear mind to to make some tough
decisions. So, um yeah, he was supposed
to be on that break, but he had other
plans and and got a job. So, I'm happy
for him.
>> Ryan, among the tough decisions, this
the salary cap math would seem to
indicate that decision to make ads with
his contract. Where does that stand
right now?
>> Yeah, we got to make um there's a couple
guys we got to make decisions on. Um you
know, if that's
trade, release, um there's a lot of
different options that or few options
that we can go down um to create some
space. Um like I said before, you know,
this is a unique situation where we've
got our roster in a position where, you
know, we have a lot of talented players,
a lot of guys getting paid well. Um, and
that puts some constraints on on the
cap. So, we got to make some tough
decisions. And, you know, like I said,
when we win games, you create these
relationships. There's leadership guys
or guys that were captains. Um, that
mean a lot to our organization. Um, but
when you're kind of put in a corner,
that's what the league's meant to do.
>> Is there a limit how many restructures
you you can do to to push things kind of
down the line a little bit?
>> Um, I don't know about like limited
amount of restructures, but there's a f
a lot. Sorry, I can't speak. There's um
philosophical things that we believe in
in terms of not getting to this place
where we're kicking the can down the
road on a bunch of guys and then at some
point you got to pay that bill. And you
don't want that to be the reason why
you're not flexible and and able to do
um unique things or take advantage of
opportunities with your roster.
>> In the past when you cut a veteran,
>> you've done so before the combine kind
of out of you know give them time. Is
this kind of new schedule that you guys
are on is that can we read into that as
to why that wasn't necessarily the case
this time around if you do end up
cutting the guy?
>> I wouldn't read too much into it. Um we
just got to go through the process um to
see what avenue, you know, or what path
we want to go down.
>> What was your big picture evaluation of
DJ's season?
>> Yeah. Uh, I think you know early on with
you have a lot of new things going on
and there's a lot of um there's one
football and there's a lot more talented
targets and how that all works out where
they I can't tell you like where
everybody is in different progressions.
So I know at some points it was slow
some moments like you know towards the
end of the season was amazing. Um I
think when you looked at the production
across the board of all our guys it came
out to be pretty even in terms of
targets and yards. Um, so I thought he
did a really good job. I know Ben was
very intentional with with getting him
the football to create opportunities.
Um, but when you have Coulson start to
pop up, Luther Hole, um, Rome was going
through different things throughout the
season, but started hot early. Um, so
unique situation overall. Um, but I know
we were happy with him throughout the
tone with him in the exit interview just
setting him up for what he can expect in
the future.
>> Yeah. Um, very similar to the other guys
went through the season. um the exit
meeting, we we also want to know what
what they need from us um to help them
be successful. Um but real positive
conversation with with DJ and and really
everybody on the
>> roster
those question marks, those gray areas
on the roster are settled in your mind
as guys you want to keep going forward
such as or
>> um yeah, we're working through that. Um,
I feel pretty good about the guys who
just mentioned um being here, but again
um there's a lot more calls coming in on
on interest on some of these guys. Um,
so we have to kind of sequence that out
to see how it impacts our team. Um, I
talked about a little bit of cost of
replacement. Um, so what does that look
like? Um, so really this week is kind of
we know what we need to do, but any new
unique opportunities that might pop up
are usually going to pop up here and
then we'll get back and kind of sort it
all out and make decisions. But um, feel
pretty good about those guys.
>> Right. Flexibility is a word you use a
lot. How do you balance that with your
roster that feels like it's ready to win
draft? How do you balance that with
future?
>> Yeah, it's just the sustainability. Um,
how can we stay flexible and And that's
it's both end thinking. How can we be
successful? Take advantage of, you know,
we talked about this quarterback window,
take advantage of that, but also set
oursel up to to continue to win. Um, I
mentioned this earlier in one of the
interviews. I mean, um, I got a head
coach that wants to sustain success and
win for a long period of time. I have a
quarterback um, who continues to
progress and and he wants to be one of
the best to ever do it and win a lot of
championships. Um, so with that model,
we have to be very conscious of how we
put this team together, but we want to
win championships now. We want to be
able to have that flexibility to
continue to win down the road, too.
>> You want to do both, but if you had to
rank them between winning now versus
winning over the next five years, like
which one just in a vacuum where you
>> I wish I lived in a vacuum. Um, but
yeah, you got to win the first one,
right? Like you got to get started. Um,
but what are you willing to sacrifice to
do that? Like there's some things you
can do to, and you all have seen that
before I got here, you can accelerate it
and then after it goes away pretty
quick. Um, so we got to balance both.
Um, unfortunately that's not reality in
terms of, you know, picking it and and
do you want to go all in and hurt
yourself down the road? We our mindset
is to to do both. Um, win now and then
be able to sustain that and have
flexibility. So, it's not going to be
easy. You know what I mean? Like, I can
guarantee you, you know, we've been
really good with dead money. At some
point, that's going to go up, too,
because that's just the nature of of of
playing this out over a long period of
time and having tough decisions to make.
>> We've been told that tight end is one of
the harder positions for guys to
transition to from college to the NFL,
but like Coulson success, Tyler Warren
had a ton of success. Do you think
there's a greater positional emphasis on
drafting a first round tight end? I
mean, considering how it worked out for
you guys last year,
>> I think the impact that they have on a
quarterback is is key there. Um,
obviously, I think it's unique to have
two guys like that that start hot like
that. Um, I think how they were raised
their foundation in college, their
intelligence played a part in that. And,
um, you know, one was with a younger
quarterback, the other one was someone a
little bit more experienced um, that was
quick to get the ball out. Um, I think
the coordinators do a really good job,
you know, using that position to
manipulate defenses, too, and create
mismatches. Um, especially out of 12
personnel. So, um, really fortunate to
have Coulson. I think he elevates our
entire team and helps Caleb touch on the
offensive tackle as there. I think you
said that you don't expect Azie [snorts]
deep into the season. You talked to us
at interview.
>> Are you expecting him to come back?
Like, I mean, is this injury that how
significant is that for him in the rehab
process?
>> Yeah, he'll miss most of the year, but
we expect him to come back and heal from
it. I mean, there's a plan in place. Um,
I can't get into like timelines or
anything like that. I just don't know.
Uh, but yeah, we expect him to be back
and and be himself, but uh, you know,
pretty significant injuries that he's
got to get through, but in terms of
affecting his overall career or next
year, I don't see that being an issue.
>> You talked about best player available,
but when you're 25 and you're stack your
board the way you stack it no matter
what. Does anything shift when you're at
the bottom of the round versus when you
can you take a risk on a guy because you
know gamble on the ceiling or or is it
all the same?
>> Yeah, I think if you look at you know
some late round action and and
historically
um I think you want to just stay
disciplined with taking good football
players. I think, you know, you can take
a little risk and and I mentioned this
before, you can go get a flashy guy that
may not be, you know, the wiring in
terms of culture fit isn't the the right
thing to do. So, you take a chance there
or um you know, it's flashes or they're
young player and you're going to project
this crazy growth. I think taking good
football players at 25 and not, you
know, I think back to the Steelers. I
think back to the Ravens and some of
these teams that just were able to put
really good rosters together and draft
well late. Um, if you those guys aren't
sexy, like they're just good, hardy
football players. So, that's what we're
going to focus on. Um, I think that'll
put our our team in the best position to
be successful.
>> Do you keep up? Do you It's kind of off
the top a little bit. Do you keep up
with the stadium stuff? Do you have
people texting you asking you if the
Bears are
you keep up with?
>> I have enough to worry about with the
football team. Um, yes. Text random
calls of people I don't know how they
have my number to being in Grand Cayman
and bumping up in the pool and start
telling me about where they want the
stadium. So, um, yeah, I got a lot of
faith in in Kevin and George to um to to
get that done and and do what's best for
the organization, our fan base. Um
there's a lot of pieces involved with
that, but um like I said, I got enough
to worry about with the roster.
>> Is that your stock answer?
>> No, I just I don't say much at all.
>> Are you looking for from some of these
defensive line prospects?
>> Yeah, motor, relentlessness, uh
violence, u explosive, and then I just
want to continue to improve our
defensive speed. Um I think we saw that
a little bit Green Bay and some of the
the games down the stretch. Um, I want
to improve our our defensive speed
overall. Um, so those are some of the
factors that
>> pass for Caleb in the efficiency jump
that you want to see this next season
with him.
>> Yeah. I And and I'm not trying to dodge
a question. I think asking Ben that will
probably give you the best answer to it.
Um,
>> yeah, I'll stick with that.
>> You guys were here. You were still in
you had a clear vision, but now a year
later, how much more confident are you
in just your processes through this part
of this?
>> Yeah, really confident. Um we've had a
lot of conversations. Um he's even
popped into our draft meetings this past
go around where last year put his staff
he wasn't able to do that as much. Uh so
earlier jump on that and then through
conversations with him and and DA just
in terms of what they what they're
looking for to create an advantage or to
improve a unit um the style that we want
to play. The more that we talk and go
through and watch guys and have
conversations about our own guys the
more clarity we get from what they want.
Um, and as a front office, that's all we
want to give them is guys that they want
to work with.
>> And Jamar, two guys. Can you just give
us kind of a sense of your outlook for
both those guys just in terms of both
their injury and then what you kind of
saw from them during the season?
>> Yeah, [snorts] so Dio was a little bit
unfortunate. He was the guy we brought
in that we wanted to work inside and
outside. Um, and due to some of the
injuries, I thought Book was coming
along in training camp. um he had a I
think a knee injury at some point in the
beginning. So we really didn't get to
flex as much as we wanted to um to try
to improve our rush from the you know
interior and exterior. Um but he was
coming along. There was a lot of uh
positive things there both in the run
which I know we don't talk much about
but getting to third down is a huge
deal. Um so I thought he was coming
along and we're looking forward to him
coming back. I know he's training and in
his return to play protocol. Uh Shamar
was another one uh has flex that we were
trying to find out where he was gonna be
the most productive and it was coming
along at end um which was great um
because he would have versatility inside
and outside which is what we want and um
so it was a bummer kind of a freak deal
with him and his knee uh both guys are
on track training hard um again you know
I'm hoping in the spring but if anything
training camp will be the spot where
they come back and there's a process
through that of of playing the game and
uh getting comfortable and healthy that
we'll go through. But I expect both
those guys to help us next year.
>> But what's your evaluation of the left
tackle class and do you think there's a
starter to be had at 25?
>> Yeah. Um I think the the tackle position
is uh pretty healthy this year. Um not
sure. Sometimes, you know, there's years
where there's a run um where they're all
gone. There's a lot of them. Sometimes
there's a couple guys that are are
sitting there waiting for you. Um, so
we'll see how it shakes out. Um, but
yeah, that's that's a unique situation
for us trying to determine how to fill
that that space um with what we have. I
know, you know, we want to keep Darnell
and Jonah together. We got a really cool
right side. Um, so then there's there's
draft, there's free agency, what's the
cost of agency, there's resigning your
own with Braxton, and then you have
Theo's development. Um we've yet to put
a whole offseason together with Karan,
but he showed promise at times. Um so a
lot of different factors that are a
little bit difficult to figure out.
>> To clarify clarify and DJ to clarify and
DJ um is he one of the players you feel
good about being here in 2026 or do you
have to entertain some different
conversations just because of his
contract and your salary cap?
>> Yeah, I I gotta have conversations and
kind of see what like I said the best
combination of players we can bring in.
Um, we want him here. Um, we think
highly of him. Um, he's a great
teammate. He's been productive pretty
consistently over the last couple years
that he's been here. Um, so I have
nothing but great things to say about
him. But this is the time now where we
have to look at all the different
scenarios and see what can make what can
allow us to put the best team out there.
Um, and I've talked about this before.
It's just, you know, there's there's
relationships there. There's a lot there
that make it really really difficult,
but um he's a guy we we want here, but
we have to look at all different
scenarios.
>> Would it be on the table for you guys to
at left tackle with Tony as a longer
term solution or is that was that only
something you would do in a pinch?
>> I would say only in a pinch. Um we like
him at left guard. Um that's where we
like him to play next year.
>> Ryan, soft tissue injuries ends up
impacting your season quite a bit. I'm
just curious how do you view those as
more of an individual basis thing or is
there something organizationally that
you guys are attacking this offseason?
>> Yeah, so we we we look at both from the
individual standpoint um you know how
they how they walked into the injury. We
also look at it from our from our
performance team support science digging
into any any things that we can do to
change to help. Um, I do think the one
factor no one's really talked about was
last year was unique in the sense that
we had u the first week was our first
by-week was in week five. Um, and then
we had Friday games, we had Saturday
games, Sunday games. We never really had
a Thursday game. If you go back to a
couple years ago, there's like a really
sweet setup that we had was Thursday in
the first quarter, Thursday in the
second quarter by week the last possible
weekend. It was the most healthy team
that we had. So I think a little bit of
a schedule a little bit is you know you
do have a new staff guys are trying to
prove themselves the output is way
higher um which you do try to manage
through your sport science um but to
kind of sum it up we look through it
from a team perspective what can we do
better but we have to look at all the
factors that could have led to it too
because you know just resulting we don't
want to you know create some chaos and
redo everything um because we might be
doing the right thing it just was the
scenario and the environment in terms of
the
Just a couple days after the season, Ben
was really emphatic about saying, "We're
back at square one. We're back at the
bottom." What do you think was the
significance of being so
>> quick and emphatic with that message?
>> Yeah, just look across the the league in
in the last I mean forever. The moment
you get comfortable and think you can
take success from one year and just
apply it to the next um you can be in
for a rude awakening. Um the mindset
that we have to have is starting fresh.
um rebuilding the foundation that we had
um and then improving where we need to
improve and specifically like where our
struggles are. Um if we have that
mindset will be we'll be good. If the
mindset is we'll be good uh just because
we're good last year um I think you're
setting yourself up for for failure. the
work that the guys put in our coaching
put in our front office, our whole
organization. We have to really exceed
that to be even better than what we were
last year. There's going to be
challenges. I think I said it a few
years ago, something will happen that,
you know, we're not planned for that we
have to adjust and adapt to. Sometimes
you're healthy most of the season,
sometimes you're injured, how you adapt
to that. So, every season is unique. And
I think what Ben was doing was
establishing the mindset of we got to go
back to work in order to get to where we
need to go. Awesome. Thank you guys.
>> Okay, let's start with this. I know what
everyone's thinking. Does Caleb have NBA
aspirations?
>> And the answer is no.
>> I think football is his calling. Did you
see the three-point contest?
>> You feel better? Were you worried?
>> Well, I sent I sent him
>> I sent him a meme of a guy just missing
left and right like before and then when
it actually happened, I felt bad.
[laughter]
I was like, "Whoops." Spoke that one
into existence, didn't I? So anyways,
let's open it up guys.
>> Yeah. Yeah, he did. It was. Thank
Thanks, Jason. [laughter]
Thanks for the reminder.
>> At [snorts] the end of the season, you
were pretty intentional about saying
nothing carries over. We are starting a
fresh. Why was it so important you get
that message out there last year?
>> Yeah. Well, I mean, we we fell short of
our ultimate goal, which was to to win
the championship. And so, uh, the
biggest thing is we don't confuse the,
uh, you know, a postseason victory or,
uh, you know, exceeding expectations
from outside of the building that is,
uh, okay to be complacent. It It's not
It's not We didn't do enough. And so, we
got we got to do more. We got to give
more than what we gave a year ago.
Coaching staff, players, uh, every
everyone in that building, we have to do
a little bit more. So when you look at
it that way, yeah, we are back to ground
zero and we got to continue to build on
this thing. Now, does that mean when we
come back in the spring that we're not
going to be uh further along offensively
or defensively than we were the previous
spring? No, that's not what that means.
But yet, it does help frame our mindset
that we are going to have to give more.
>> Ben, uh, how did you assess the
defensive line and what attributes are
you looking to bring to the building,
whether it's through draft or
>> Yeah. Well, I we're still going through
that that process right now. Just uh
free agency. We there's some guys out
there that we feel like could help us
out. Uh we certainly feel feel uh good
about some of the guys that we currently
have in the building that they'll
continue to ascend and take the coaching
that, you know, DA and and the defensive
staff are are providing for them. Um
but, you know, for us to take the next
step as a defense, we do need to
pressure the quarterback at a more
consistent clip. And so, that is a point
of emphasis for us. Uh I do think this
draft uh does have some guys that could
possibly help us out in that regard. Um
but that that'll be something that we
got to look at. Uh and it and it will be
a point of emphasis when we come back in
the springtime. Just how do we increase
our get off to where we can we can put
more pressure on the queue here before
the inside out on the D line. Is that
still the priority or do you think like
edge is a bigger priority in this class?
Yeah, we just need good football players
all across the board. And so, uh, as far
as I'm concerned, I I don't I don't mind
so much if it's if that's interior rush,
oh, sure, we'll take it. If that's, uh,
the the guy that's on the edge fits the
bill, sure, we'll take that as well.
But, um, I'm not going to pigeon hole us
into saying that we have to build this
roster.
Ryan's not going to do the same thing
either. Um, you know, we we just want to
find some really good football players
that love to play the game, that love to
compete, that want to win football
games. Um, and and we'll figure it out
from there.
>> What are the advantages Caleb has being
in the offse
in terms of knowing what you want and
also, you know, how much growth can be
made because, you know, it's not new
anymore, you know, you know, focusing
in.
>> Yeah. Well, I mean, we saw um enormous
growth over the course of the season.
And you know, I keep going back to what
seven on seven looked like at the end of
the year versus what it looked like to
start the year. Uh, a drill as simple as
that. And yet, you see him uh look so
much more comfortable going through some
of those same plays. You know, a lot of
it was like riding the bike for the
first time with with some of these
concepts. You just hadn't seen it. And
uh and you get thrown a different
coverage each and every time. Um, now
you can accelerate your vision a little
bit more. And and that's what he's
learned to do. And I that's where I'm
really confident the direction he's
going. Uh I'm excited for him. Um I
think he's going to be able to look at
some of these cutups from the self scout
and look at what he could have done a
little bit better. Um I'm I think what's
most encouraging to me is something
happened at the end of the year where I
showed him one thing on tape and uh
didn't even think it would come up in
the in the next game and yet it did. and
and then he threw the ball to the exact
spot that I would have wanted him to
throw the ball to. Now, the result of
the play wasn't what we wanted to for
for other reasons. And yet, something as
simple as that, I'm like, "Holy cow,
this if if this guy can take one little
nugget that we talked about the week
prior and we really weren't emphasizing
and yet be able to apply that real time
in a game, um, man, he's he's really
going to ascend quickly." And so, I'm
looking forward to it. Um, I I really do
think this this next off season we'll
see significant strides.
>> As you push for greater efficiency from
him, what's the next step for him and
becoming more efficient?
>> Yeah. Well, I mean, I think there's no
question that there'll be some throws
last year that um he needs to complete
or or give a more catchable ball at a
higher rate and and he'll be the first
one to tell you that. Um, you know, we
as a coaching staff take a lot of pride
in trying to get the primary guy open
and uh if we are able to do that, he's
he's going to come through and he's
going to make that throw. And then if we
can't do that for him from a coaching
perspective or play calling perspective,
then he makes us right, you know, and
and that's where his his magical talent,
you know, can can uh be the ultimate
eraser for us and fixer. Um, so it's the
balance between the two and uh I'm look,
like I said, I'm looking forward to
mechanically he was learning some
different things with his footwork. Um,
it was it actually looked more
comfortable to him than I would have
thought year one and and yet I really
think a full off season of really
drilling that down home is going to help
him be more accurate here going forward.
>> How much have they changed you as a
player? Maybe not just as a player, but
also like setting up game.
Um, yeah, significantly. I mean,
everything you do is driven by the
players that you have. And so, um, not
just him, but all of our perimeter
players, our running backs, our O line,
you know, I I think about plays with
them in mind. Um, certainly. And so, it
it's all the above. Um, you don't you
don't want to put the onus on just one
guy to where he's got to carry the
burden for the entire offense, the
course of the game. Um, you do want them
to be able to know when when their
number's called, hey, we really need you
to come through in this moment because
because this is where you got the the
big hat, you know, you gota we we need
you on this. And I I think the guys
throughout the throughout the offense,
they answer the bell in that regard.
>> With DJ Moore, um, you know, his name is
out there is kind of having a little bit
of an uncertain future. We know the
statistics that he had. What was his
value to your offense this past season?
>> Yeah, it was immense. Um he he probably
knew knew all the roles of the receivers
better than anybody else we had in that
room. You know, X, Z, F, it really
didn't matter. He was a guy we knew we
could count on. Um if guys go down, he
could step in. Um he there really wasn't
anything we'd shy away from in terms of
the route tree that that he could or
could not do. Uh and so I feel like the
versatility is something that screams at
you. The intelligence screams at you.
And then as Ryan alluded to in our last
press conference, just the toughness,
the durability, um when [snorts] you
when you talk about 17 plus game season,
that's where a player like that is is
really really valuable.
>> Ben, how difficult was it to pick an OC
among the candidates?
>> Say that again.
>> Uh how difficult was it for you to pick
an offensive coordinator among the
candidates that you had on staff?
>> Yeah. No, I I think let me start by
saying this. You know, you lose two
really good coaches in in Eric Benemy
and Declan Doyle. I I can't say enough
about either one of those two guys and
the contributions that they made last
year um in in their own way. I I think
uh we've been very very much a proponent
of wanting guys to move on and if they
find another role or another job that
they feel like uh they want to take a
shot at, then then I'm all for it. And
uh you know, I think both those teams,
both uh Kansas City and and Baltimore,
are getting two really phenomenal people
and football coaches. But when it when
it comes to replacing them, I felt
strongly about Eric Studsville. He's a
guy I've worked with in in the past. I I
think he'll do a great job in our
running back room and bring some
different things to the table. Uh for
offensive coordinator, yeah, we went uh
around and and we interviewed outside of
the building. Um, certainly we have a
number of guys in the building that I
feel very strongly about as well, not
just press. Um, I think when you put
together a staff, that's really what you
want to do is you want to see, hey, can
I picture the young coaches becoming
position coaches? Can I picture some of
the position coaches becoming
coordinators and then possibly even head
coaches one day? And I I do I believe we
we've got some guys that fit that mold
on on really both sides of the ball. And
so, uh, I'm fortunate to have that on
this staff. Um Press in particular was a
guy that checked all the boxes of what I
was looking for. He did a phenomenal job
last year. He's he's very smart, very
detailed. Um did some things behind the
scenes that that people probably don't
realize and and yet I I know he's got
the respect of these players.
>> What are the biggest things you need
from [clears throat]
as a play caller? What do you want from
your
>> Well, yeah, I I'm not in every single
staff meeting. Uh I'm not in every
single offensive meeting with the
players. summon as many of them that I
that I can attend that time allows. And
so it's just the understanding that
nothing skips a beat when when I have to
leave the room. And uh you know, Press
has been there. He's done that. That's
that's the good thing about it. And uh I
I hold him in really high regard. He's
he's uh he's done a phenomenal job in
the in the role last year as pass game
coordinator, and I've got nothing but
immense confidence that he he'll do a
great job here as a coordinator as well.
We talked [snorts] to Ryan about the
balance of the short-term versus
long-term roster construction and some
of the salary cap situations. From just
your coaching standpoint, I know you
know Ryan handles a lot of a lot of
that, but how do you look at it? How do
you kind of approach this off season and
the decisions that you made when you're
obviously you want to win now, but you
also want to think about the long term
as well.
>> Yeah. No, I think that's a balancing act
and that's where where Ryan and Matt
Feinstein, um Jeff King, th those guys,
they do a great job keeping uh the big
picture in mind of what we're trying to
do shortterm and long term and and
balancing act. And so you might have an
off-the-wall idea and you kind of got to
talk it through of of what the
consequences might be um if you went
down that road. And so, uh, that's this
time of year, you know, you're you're
trying to, as I've been saying all day
long, trying to accumulate the best
90man roster you possibly can. Uh, we
needed to be as competitive as it's ever
been so that so that we take the next
step. And I know Ryan and I see our
current roster, the guys that are under
contract, very much in the same lens.
And, uh, we're totally committed to to
uh, whatever it takes to get better.
>> What did you What did you take away from
last year, Jason? Did you take away from
much in Seattle this year? talked a year
ago about watching Philadelphia and how
they had waves of defensive linemen
coming in. Was there anything from
Seattle that stood out to you as you
kind of track the way the league is
going and what you're up against?
>> Yeah. Well, I mean, I've had a lot of
respect for that particular defensive
philosophy for for a long time. Um, you
know, back Baltimore to I know he was at
Michigan for a little bit, but um I I
got to see it up close and personal and
and I think he does a heck of a job. you
know, he's a really good uh play caller
on the defensive side of the ball. Um,
anytime you're able to stop the run,
playing too high defense, I I think you
got something good going and and yet
they were still able to rush the the
quarterback with only four as well. And
so, um, I think they did a great job.
You know, John Snider has done a great
job with that roster. Um I I haven't
gone back and watched that particular
game, but uh from afar, immense amount
of respect for what they did this year.
>> Thanks, guys.
>> Yeah. Thank you.
>> You know, you told Caleb to get away
from football. Maybe this basketball.
>> Yeah, I I think I think it's time to
come on back now. Children.